William R. Cotter Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
William R. Cotter Papers.
undated, 1970-1981.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Center.
Cotter, William R.
179.8 linear feet.
William R. Cotter, Democratic Member of Congress for the First District of Connecticut, was born in Hartford, Connecticut on 18 July 1926. In 1953, Cotter was elected to the Hartford Court of Common Council, and served as an aide to United States Senator Abraham Ribicoff, 1955-1957, as Deputy Insurance Commissioner, 1957-1964, and as Insurance Commissioner of Connecticut from 1964-1970. He developed and introduced laws to regulate rates and solvency of insurance companies in Connecticut, and developed a comprehensive automobile liability insurance reform program. Cotter was elected to the ninety-second Congress on November 3, 1970 and was reelected five times. He represented the First District in Connecticut from 1971 until his death.
MSS19910002
Biography
William R. Cotter, Democratic Member of Congress for the First District of Connecticut, was born in Hartford, Connecticut on 18 July 1926. He attended public schools, and received a bachelor's degree in economics and history from Trinity College (Hartford) in 1949. In 1953, Cotter was elected to the Hartford Court of Common Council, and served as an aide to United States Senator Abraham Ribicoff (1955-1957), as Deputy Insurance Commissioner (1957-1964), and as Insurance Commissioner of Connecticut (1964-1970). He developed and introduced laws to regulate rates and solvency of insurance companies in Connecticut, and developed a comprehensive automobile liability insurance reform program.
Cotter was elected to the ninety-second Congress on 3 November 1970 and was reelected five times. He represented the First District in Connecticut from 1971 until his death. The towns Cotter represented varied over the years, but included Berlin, Bloomfield, Bolton, Cromwell, East Hartford, East Windsor, Glastonbury, Hartford, Wethersfield, Windsor, and much of Portland. As a congressional representative, Cotter served on the Banking and Currency Committee, and the Science and Astronautics Committee. He was also an active member of the House Ways and Means Committee. William Cotter died on 8 September 1981.
Scope and Content
The collection contains newspaper clippings, information on legislative bills, correspondence, executive and campaign records, grant files, questionnaires, press releases, and various Connecticut Town files. There is very little personal material.
The materials added to the collection in 2006 have not been processed but the box numbers and rough inventory information has been incorporated into the appropriate series as part of the description of the collection.
Arrangement
Series I: Legislative Correspondence ( 1971-1981 )
Series II: Executive Records ( 1971-1981 )
Series III: Voting Records ( 1977-1981 )
Series IV: Bill File ( 1973-1980 )
Series V: Campaign Records ( 1970-1976 )
Series VI: Press Releases ( 1975-1980 )
Series VII: Meeting Notices and Schedules ( 1971-1978 )
Series VIII: Questionnaire Replies ( 1974-1975 )
Series IX: State and Town Files ( undated, 1971-1978 )
Series X: Grant Files ( 1977-1981 )
Series XI: Project Files ( undated, 1971-1981 )
Series XII: Personal Correspondence ( 1971-1979 )
Series XIII: Redistricting Materials ( 1970-1973 )
Series XIV: Office Management Files ( 1971-1979 )
Series XV: Speech Files ( 1970-1980 )
Series XVI: Topic Files ( undated, 1972-1980 )
Series XVII: Audiovisual materials ( undated )
Series XVIII: Unsorted materials ( undated, 1970-1981 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut's Congressional delegation. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
United States. Congress. House—Members' papers—Connecticut.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Ways and Means.; Connecticut—Politics and government—1951-
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Personal Papers.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Newspaper Clippings.; Press Releases.
Occupations:
Politician.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
The Papers were transferred to the Connecticut State Library by the late Representative Cotter's office staff in October 1981. Some additional records remained in the Washington and Hartford offices, and some materials of no historical value were destroyed by agreement.
Acquisition Information
In February 1991, the papers were deaccessioned by the State Library and transferred to the University of Connecticut Libraries. A deed of ownership dated 15 September 1991, signed by Elizabeth Cotter Adinolfi, sister of William R. Cotter, transferred ownership of the papers to the University of Connecticut.
In 2006, the University of Hartford Library transferred Cotter materials that had been donated to them by Mr. Adolfino.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Legislative Correspondence, 1971-1981
  - House of Representatives: Rules and Seniority System, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Appropriations
    - Science, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Health, Education, Welfare, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Armed Services: draft, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Banking and Currency, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Education and Labor, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Government Operations, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - House Administrations, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 11)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 12)
  - Internal Security, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 13)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 14)
  - Judiciary, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 15)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 16)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 17)
  - Public Works, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 18)
  - Rules, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 19)
  - Science and Astronautics, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 20)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 21)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
  - Ways and Means, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 23)
  - Select Committees, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 24)
  - Joint Committees, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 25)
  - House of Representatives, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 27)
  - Appropriations, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 28)
  - Armed Services, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 29)
  - Banking and Currency
    - General, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 30)
    - Finance, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 31)
    - Mesbie, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 32)
    - Housing, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 33)
  - District of Columbia, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 34)
  - Education and Labor: Jud Gun Control, 1972 (Box 4:, Folder 35)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 36)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 37)
  - Public Works, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 38)
  - Rules, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 39)
  - Science and Astronautics, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 40)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 41)
  - Veterans' Affairs, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 42)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 43)
    - Imports: cat and dog skins, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 44)
    - Imports, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 45)
    - National Health Insurance, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 46)
    - Oil Imports, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 47)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 48)
    - Special Security and Welfare, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 49)
    - Taxes, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 50)
    - Tax Reform: parochial and private school tuition, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 51)
  - Select Committees, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 52)
  - Joint Committees, 1972 (Box 5:, Folder 53)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 54)
  - Agriculture: general, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 55)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Agriculture, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 57)
    - Foreign Operations, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 58)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 59-60)
    - Health, Education, Welfare Appropriations Bill, DED Funding, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 61)
  - Armed Services, 1973 (Box 5:, Folder 62)
  - Banking and Currency
    - General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 63)
    - Community Development Revenue Sharing, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 64)
    - Cotter Amendments, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 65)
    - Economic Stability Act, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 66)
    - Housing, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 67)
    - Mass Transit Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 68)
  - District of Columbia, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 69)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 70)
    - Education, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 71)
    - Labor, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 72)
  - Energy, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 73)
  - Foreign Affairs
    - General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 74)
    - Emergency Security/HR 11088 (assistance for Israel), 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 75)
    - Southeast Asia, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 76)
  - Government Operations: General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 77)
  - House Administration: General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 78)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs: General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 79)
  - Internal Security: General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 80)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce
    - General, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 81)
    - Alaskan Pipeline, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 82)
    - Broadcast Licensing, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 83)
    - HR 7200 (RR retirement), 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 84)
    - HR 643 (FDA regulation on vitamins), 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 85)
  - Judicial
    - Anti-abortion, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 86)
    - Pro-abortion, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 87)
    - Buckley, Michael P. (HR 12 and HR 6449), 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 88)
    - Ford Nomination, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 89)
    - Special Prosecutor, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 90)
    - Anti-impeachment, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 91)
    - Petitions and Calls, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 92)
    - Watergate and Impeachment, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 93)
  - Impeachment
    - A, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 94)
    - B, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 95-96)
    - C, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 97-98)
    - D, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 99)
    - E - Z, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 100)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1973 January - June (Box 8:, Folder 101)
    - 1973 July - December (Box 8:, Folder 102)
    - Beagle Pups Issue, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 103)
    - Executive vs. Congress, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 104)
    - Library of Congress, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 105)
    - Response to Newsletter, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 106)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 107)
  - Public Works, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 108)
  - Rules: General, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 109)
  - Science and Astronautics: General, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 110)
  - Small Business: General, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 111)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 112)
  - Veterans Affairs
    - General, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 113)
    - Effect of 20% Increase on VA Pension, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 114)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 115)
    - Foreign Imports, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 116)
    - National Health Plan, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 117)
    - HR 4200 and Pension Reform, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 118)
    - Social Security, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 119)
    - Social Security Benefits Increase, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 120)
    - Taxes, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 121)
    - HR 49 (Tax Credit for Private School Tuition), 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 122)
  - Select Committees
    - General, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 123-124)
    - Crime, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 125)
  - Joint Committee on Budget: Review, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 126)
  - Northeast Congressional Caucus, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 127)
  - Connecticut, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 128)
  - Agriculture, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 129)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 130)
    - Health, Education, Welfare, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 131-132)
  - Armed Services, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 133)
  - Banking and Currency
    - General, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 134)
    - Housing, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 135)
  - District of Columbia, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 136)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 137)
    - Labor, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 138)
    - Education, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 139)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 140)
  - Government Operations, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 141)
  - House Administration, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 142)
  - House Reform, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 143)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 144)
  - Internal Security, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 145)
  - IFC, 1974 July - December (Box 11:, Folder 146)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 147)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 148)
    - Pro-abortion, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 149)
    - Nelson Rockefeller Nomination, Vice President, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 150)
    - Nixon's Status After Resignation Petitions, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 151)
    - Judiciary
      - Pro-Impeachment, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 152)
      - Anti-Impeachment, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 153)
    - Anti-Impeachment, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 154)
    - Pro-Impeachment, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 155)
    - Pro-Impeachment, B - Z, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 156)
    - Nixon Impeachment proceedings, instructions for Congressmen, undated (Box 132)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1974 (Box 12:, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous
  - 1974 January - June (Box 13:, Folder 158)
  - 1974 July - December (Box 13:, Folder 159)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 160)
  - Public Works, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 161)
  - Rules, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 162)
  - Science and Astronautics, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 163)
  - Small Business, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 164)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 165)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 166)
    - Taxes, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 167)
    - Tax Reform, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 168)
    - Trade, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 169)
    - Social Security, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 170)
  - Joint Committee, 1974 (Box 13:, Folder 171)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 172)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 173)
  - Agriculture, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 174)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 175)
    - Foreign Operations, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 176)
    - Health, Education, Welfare - Health, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 177)
    - Health, Education, Welfare - Education, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 178)
  - Armed Services, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 179)
  - Banking and Currency
    - Housing, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 180)
    - Aid to New York City, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 181)
  - Budget, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 182)
  - District of Columbia, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 183)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 184)
    - Education, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 185)
    - Labor, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 186)
    - Labor - HR 5900, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 187)
  - Government Operations
    - General, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 188)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 189)
  - House Administrations, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 190)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 191)
  - International Relations
    - Re H.Lon.Res. 393, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 192)
    - Aid to Turkey, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 193)
    - Aid to Middle East, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 194)
    - Aid to S.E.A., 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 195)
  - International and Foreign Commerce
    - 1975 January - June (Box 15:, Folder 196)
    - 1975 July - December (Box 15:, Folder 197)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 198)
    - Pro-Meskill Nomination, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 199)
    - Anti-Meskill Nomination, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 200)
    - Gun Control, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 201)
    - Aid to V.M. refugees, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 202)
    - Internal Security: General, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 203)
    - Pro-abortion, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 204)
    - Anti-abortion, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 205)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 206)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1975 January - March (Box 16:, Folder 207)
    - 1975 March - June (Box 16:, Folder 208)
    - 1975 July - September (Box 16:, Folder 209)
    - 1975 October - December (Box 16:, Folder 210)
    - South Catholic High School Project, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 211)
  - Post Office and Civil Service, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 212)
  - Public Works, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 213)
  - Rules
    - General, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 214)
    - House Reform, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 215)
  - Science and Technology, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 216)
  - Small Business, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 217)
  - Standards of Office Conduct: General, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 218)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 219)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 220)
    - Health Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 221)
    - National Health, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 222)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 223)
    - Ford Tax Cut Proposal, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 224)
    - Taxes, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 225)
    - Social Security Sub: Connecticut Welfare Cases, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 226)
    - Tax Reform: LAL, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 227)
    - Tax Reform, 1975 January - March (Box 17:, Folder 228)
    - Tax Reform, 1975 April - June (Box 17:, Folder 229)
    - Tax Reform, 1975 July - September (Box 17:, Folder 230)
    - Tax Reform, 1975 October - December (Box 17:, Folder 231)
    - HR 4608, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 232)
    - Uniroyal, Inc., 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 233)
    - Energy, 1975 January - June (Box 17:, Folder 234)
    - Energy, 1975 July - December (Box 17:, Folder 235)
    - Trade, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 236)
    - Ford's Tariff and Tax Plan, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 237)
    - Social Security, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 238)
    - HR 6309 (Delay Connecticut Repayment on Unemployment Compensation), 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 239)
  - Easter Seal File, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 240)
  - Joint Committees, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 241)
  - Select Committees, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 242)
  - House of Representatives, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 243)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 244)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 245)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 246)
    - Food Stamp Reform, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 247)
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 248)
    - DOD (B-1 Bomber), 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 249)
    - Labor, HEW Subcommittee: General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 250)
    - Health, Education and Welfare: Education, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 251)
    - Health, Education and Welfare: Health, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 252)
    - RE Funds Forceta (Title II in Emer. Suppl. Bill), 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 253)
    - Foreign Operations, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 254)
  - Armed Services
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 255)
    - B-1 Bomber, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 256)
  - Banking, Currency & Housing
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 257)
    - Housing, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 258)
  - Budget
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 259)
    - RE 1st Budget Res. Col. For Veterans, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 260)
  - District of Columbia, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 261)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 262)
    - Education, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 263)
    - Labor, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 264)
  - Government Operations
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 265)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 266)
  - House Administration
    - General, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 267)
    - Reconstituting FEC, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 268)
    - House, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 269)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 270)
  - International Relations
    - General, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 271)
    - Food reserve, House Congressional Resolution 393, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 272)
    - Aid to Turkey, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 273)
    - HR 10594 (Military Sales), 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 274)
  - International and Foreign Commerce
    - 1976 January - June (Box 19:, Folder 275)
    - 1976 July - December (Box 19:, Folder 276)
    - HR 13000, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 277)
    - Natural Gas (de-regulation), 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 278)
    - HR 12323, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 279)
  - Judiciary
    - General, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 280)
    - Gun Control, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 281)
    - Internal Security, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 282)
    - Anti-abortion, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 283)
    - Pro-abortion, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 284)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 285)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 20)
    - General, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 286)
    - 1976 April - June (Box 20:, Folder 287)
    - 1976 July - september (Box 20:, Folder 288)
    - 1976 October - December (Box 20:, Folder 289)
    - N.E. Midwest Economic Coalition, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 290)
    - August Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 291)
    - Questionnaire Additional Responses, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 292)
    - Questionnaire results (returned), 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 293)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - General, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 294)
    - Elimination of 1% add on: PO & CS, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 295)
  - Public Works, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 296)
  - Rules: General, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 297)
  - Science and Technology, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 298)
  - Small Business, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 299)
  - Standards of Official Conduct, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 300)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 301)
  - Ways and Means
    - General, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 302)
    - Taxes, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 303)
    - Tax Reform, 1976 January - March (Box 21:, Folder 304)
    - Tax Reform, 1976 April - June (Box 21:, Folder 305)
    - Tax Reform, 1976 July - December (Box 21:, Folder 306)
    - 5% Investment Tax Credit, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 307)
    - Taxes (Estate and Gift Tax Reform), 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 308)
    - Dexter Corporation (Bishop Matt.), 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 309)
    - Health, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 310)
    - National Health Insurance, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 311)
    - Public Assistance, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 312)
    - Social Security, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 313)
    - Trade, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 314)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 315)
    - Oversight Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 316)
  - Joint Committee, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 317)
  - Select Committee, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 318)
  - Connecticut Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 319)
  - New England Congressional Caucus, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 320)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 321)
    - HR 7171 (Farm Bill), 1977
  - Appropriations
    - General, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 322)
    - Defense, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 323)
    - Labor, HEW Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 324)
    - HEW Subcommittee>, Hyde Amendment, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 325)
  - Armed Services, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 326)
  - Banking, Currency & Housing, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 327)
  - Budget
    - General, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 328)
    - Mitchell Transfer Amendment, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 329)
  - District of Columbia, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 330)
  - Education and Labor
    - General, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 331)
    - Education, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 332)
    - HR 3744 (Minimum Wage), 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 333)
    - HR 3500, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 334)
  - Government Operations, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 335)
  - House Administration
    - General, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 336)
    - 1977 July - December (Box 22:, Folder 337)
    - Gammage Motion, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 338)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 339)
  - International Relations
    - General, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 340)
    - Human Rights and Soviet Jewery, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 341)
  - Panama Canal Treaty, 1977 (Box 23:, Folder 342)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce